acculynx.com 2019-12-10

# Privacy Policy - Acculynx

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) discloses what information AccuLynx (“AccuLynx,” “we” or “us”) gathers about you through our website and any services provided through our website (collectively, the “Website”) and when you use our applications and any services provided through our applications (collectively the “App”), however accessed, and discloses how that information is used. AccuLynx owns and operates the Website and App, and we use the information we receive from them as described below. We do not sell your personal information.

### USING THE WEBSITE AND/OR APP AND SHARING YOUR INFORMATION WITH US, YOU CONSENT TO AND ACCEPT THE PRIVACY PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

#####  **ONLINE AND MOBILE INFORMATION PRACTICES**

We are committed to protecting your personal privacy as you visit our Website and/or App. Accordingly, this Privacy Policy informs you how we collect and use your information on our Website and through our App. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will indicate that by changing the modification date below.

#####  **INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT**

The information we collect varies depending on the type of activity you are performing on our Website or App and helps us personalize and continually improve your experience. Much of the Website and App can be accessed without providing any personal information. In all instances where we collect personal, financial, or other information through the Website and/or App, we specifically indicate that that information is being collected in order to provide you with the product or service you have requested.

#####  **ONLINE OR MOBILE ACCOUNT SERVICES**

When you access our Website or App for products or services, we may need to collect personal, financial, and/or other information in order to complete your request. The information we collect varies depending upon the product or service you are using. Examples of information we may collect for our products or services include information such as your name, company name, address, employment and financial information, address, e-mail address, credit card number, client job information, etc.

#####  **BROWSING**

When you visit our Website, we gather information including page requests (URL requests), time of your visit, your IP address, operating system, web browser software, and any cookies which were set during a previous visit to our site. IP address information is not distributed to third parties. We use this information to improve your overall experience. We use cookies to help with navigation through our web pages; they are not used to gather any personal information about users.

#####  **MOBILE LOCATION SERVICES**

An App may utilize location services on your mobile device to collect and use location data, including the real-time geographic location of your device. If you consent to the App’s utilization of location services, we may use GPS, Bluetooth, your device’s unique identifier, and/or your IP Address, along with Wi-Fi and cell tower locations, and other technologies to determine your device’s geolocation. This location data is utilized to deliver services requested by you. We do not maintain a history of the location of a device, only where your device is at any given moment. We will collect geolocation data only if you consent, and we will notify you whether the location services will be always running or only when the App is in use. You may choose to disable location services through our App or your mobile enabled wi-fi devices, but if you do so, you will not receive any notifications or services that require a geolocation. Most mobile devices provide users with the ability to disable location services. These controls are generally located in the device’s settings menu. You can also contact your mobile service carrier or your device manufacturer for more information on disabling location services.

#####  **HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

The information you provide to us is primarily used to deliver requested products and/or services and help us improve our products and services. We also use that information to deliver you or contact you about the requested products/services or information. We may also use your personal information to provide important information about products or services that you have or are using, including security risks and updates. If you elect, we may send you a newsletter relating to our company, products, or services. Additionally, we may send you information about new products and services that may be of relevant interest to you. If you do not want to receive such marketing communications from us in the future, we will provide an Opt-out link or you can let us know by e-mailing or mailing us at the below respective addresses and telling us the name and addresses that you would like removed for those communications.

#####  **WHO WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH**

We limit the release of information and we require privacy protections in our business relationships. We do not sell customer information. In addition, we may share your personal information when required by law, or with third parties that perform functions on our behalf.

#####  **COOKIES**

A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which is then stored on your system. A cookie is useful for having the browser remember specific information across several pages or between visits to a website. A cookie does not store personally identifiable information or any sensitive information. Also, our site does not read any information stored in cookies given to you from other websites, except in cases where the other website is a provider of information or functionality within our website and that cookie is necessary to make our website function correctly.

Our website makes use of cookies for the following purposes:

  * Website administration and personalization
  * Authentication
  * Completing your request
  * Analysis of page and website information that does not identify specific individuals

You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. Browsers may also be set up to display a warning when a cookie is used. You may even disable your browser from accepting cookies. In order to provide you with the best possible experience while visiting our website, please enable cookies within your browser. Some portions of our website may not function properly if cookies are disabled.

#####  **CROSS-CONTEXT AND CROSS-DEVICE COLLECTION, IDENTIFICATION, AND PERSONALIZATION**

We merge data collected from our Website and our Apps. That data could include cookie IDs, device advertising IDs and/or device IDs, transactions and browsing history, email address, and/or any other information you have entered on our Website or App. This combination of data helps us identify you, improve your experience, and create a more personalized setting. We may also link your various devices so that the content you see on one device is the same as that seen on another one of your devices.

#####  **GOOGLE ANALYTICS**

We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of this site across devices. We have implemented the Remarketing and AdWords features of Google Analytics. The Remarketing feature allows us to serve you relevant advertising on third party websites if you have visited our Website, however accessed, but does not personally or directly identify you. AdWords allows us to manage our advertising and collect information about your visit to our Website. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ad Settings](https://www.google.com/settings). You can opt out of Google Analytics without affecting how you visit the Website. For more information on opting out of being tracked by Google Analytics, [visit this Google page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

#####  **GOOGLE CALENDAR**

AccuLynx integrates with authenticated Google Calendars to allow for the display of the calendar’ events within AccuLynx. AccuLynx will also, if enabled, create new calendar events on authenticated calendars.

#####  **GOOGLE DRIVE**

AccuLynx integrates with authenticated Google Drive accounts to allow for the selection of documents to be stored within AccuLynx.

#####  **GOOGLE EMAIL**

AccuLynx will use your Google Email account identity to verify authentication to all Google applications connected to an AccuLynx account.

#####  **LEAVING OUR WEBSITE AND/OR LINKING TO THIRD PARTIES**

When you are logged into our Website or App, it is secure. Your browser URL will indicate if you are leaving a secured portion of the Website. We strive to ensure that any information you send us is safe. When you leave this Website and go to another linked site, we are not responsible for the content or availability of the linked site. Please be advised that we do not represent either the third party or you, if you enter into a transaction on the third party site. Further, the privacy and security policies of the linked site may differ from those practiced by us.

#####  **CONTROL OVER AND ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION**

We enable you to have control over the accuracy of your personal information. You can delete or change your personal information with us at any time by contacting us via a method described under “Contact Us” below.

#####  **DO NOT TRACK**

Third parties may collect information about you across different web sites, including our website. We do not currently utilize the capability to respond to web browser do not track signals or other mechanisms that provide you with the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of this information.

#####  **SECURITY POLICY & USER RESPONSIBILITIES:**

Other than your personal information, all data and information on this Website and/or App and delivered through this Website and/or App is the sole property of the Provider. OTHER THAN YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, UNDER NO CONDITION DO YOU GAIN TITLE TO THE DATA AND INFORMATION PROVIDED THROUGH THIS WEBSITE AND/OR APP NOR MAY YOU TRANSFER, DISTRIBUTE, SUBLICENSE, SELL, DISSEMINATE OR MAKE AVAILABLE ANY OF THE DATA OR INFORMATION FROM THIS WEBSITE OR THE APP OTHER THAN THE PURPOSE IT WAS PROVIDED FOR WITHOUT THE EXPRESS CONSENT OF ACCULYNX.

You acknowledge that they may be monitored by AccuLynx when using this Webite or App so that the Acculynx may protect company assets and information. AccuLynx may employ outside, third parties to assist in this process. Should AccuLynx become aware of misuse of the company’s Data, AccuLynx may report the misuser to the proper government authorities and AccuLynx may exercise any and all of its rights. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, “misuse” includes but is not limited to: 1) failing to comply with all laws and government regulations concerning the use and application of the Data; 2) failing to comply with any terms or conditions stated in the agreement with AccuLynx; or 3) using the Website and/or App in an unreasonable, inappropriate, offensive or unethical manner. By accessing the Website and/or App, all Users you consent to being monitored by AccuLynx while using the Site.

You acknowledge and accept civil and/or criminal liability for any actions that violate the security of the Website and/or App and the intellectual property of the AccuLynx, including but not limited to: (1) accessing data not intended for such user or logging onto a server or account which user is not authorized to access; (2) attempting to probe, scan or test the vulnerability of the AccuLynx’s system or network or to breach the AccuLynx’s security measures; (3) attempting to interfere in any way with the Website and/or App of host, network or any other User or customer. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, all you acknowledge that “interference” includes, but is not limited to: mail bombing, spamming, flooding, overloading or crashing the Website and/or App or submitting any programs or viruses to the Website and/or App. “Interference” also includes using any program to browse or interact with the Website and/or App that consequently disrupts the Website and/or App. AccuLynx retains any cause-of-action that may arise due to the conduct of you toward the Website and/or App and AccuLynx may pursue any and all legal actions and available remedies.

All information, data and additional provided through the Website and App is provided “as-is.” AccuLynx is not responsible for the accuracy, completeness, reliability, or usefulness of any information, material or accessed through AccuLynx. The User of this Site assumes all responsibility and risk that may arise from using the Website and/or App.

#####  **HOW TO OPT-OUT, CORRECT PERSONAL INFORMATION, OR REQUEST ADDITIONAL INFORMATION:**

We want our customers and Users to choose how their information may be used. We enable you to have control over the accuracy of your personal information. You can delete or change your personal information with us at any time. If, at any time after registering for information or ordering the service, you change your mind about receiving information from us, send us a request specifying your new choice. Simply send your request to support@accuLynx.com. Those customers and Users that wish to update their personal information may do so by contacting support@accuLynx.com. By keeping your information current, we will be able to extend future offers and services and we will be able to facilitate offers from preferred parties. Questions regarding this Statement or the practices of this Site should be directed to support@accuLynx.com or by regular mail addressed to AccuLynx, Attn: Product Support, 525 3rd Street, Suite. 100, Beloit, Wisconsin 53511.

 **Support:**  
 **M-F 7am-6pm CST**  
 **support@acculynx.com**  
 **(608) 473-3800**

 **Sales:**  
 **M-F 7am-6pm CST**  
 **sales@acculynx.com**  
 **(866) 981-5969**
